# **ASHWIN K SHENOY**

FRONT END ENGINEER

**PHONE** : +91-9686471946

**EMAIL** : ashwinkshenoy@gmail.com

**ADDRESS**: 37, B1 SFS, 7th B Main, Yelahanka New Town,

Bangalore - 560064

#### **PROFILE**

Senior front end engineer with 6+ years experience working in a startup environment. Adept at researching and crafting pixel perfect, beautiful and elegant looking websites with good UI/UX, for a wide variety of clients and products.

## **EDUCATION**

R L J INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY | 2014

Computer Science Engineering

### SKILLS

 $\mathsf{HTML}$ 

CSS / SCSS

**JAVASCRIPT** 

**VUEJS** 

VUEX

NUXT

REACT

REDUX NODEJS

FIGMA

ILLUSTRATOR

ashwinshenoy.com



inkedin.com/in/ashwinkshenoy

0

0

# **EXPERIENCE**

O MONEYSMART - SINGAPORE

SENIOR FRONT END/UX ENGINEER | NOV 2018 - NOV 2019

Split moneysmart.sg website into separate front end (VueJS) from old backend (Rails).

Revamped modules like car insurance & provider end to end integrations.

Developed a common design system library in VueJS to be used across different tribes.

RENTOMOJO - BANGALORE

SENIOR FRONT END ENGINEER | JUN 2017 - NOV 2018

Migrated rentomojo.com website from AngularJS to VueJS. Revamped modules like Product Page, User Dashboard & Home Page.

Worked with service workers in making the complete website PWA and more mobile friendly.

Training junior developers + Code Reviews.

O FOOFYS SOLUTIONS - BANGALORE

| FRONT END ENGINEER | MAY 2014 - JUN 2017

Managed development, UX, analytics, devops and localization for various clients (Html, Scss,Angular, VueJs, Php, Rails).

Few selected projects include:

- spykk.com
- huzzpa.com (Bangalore & Mumbai)
- hopwit.me
- shenoychanakya.com

O RETAILON - BANGALORE

INTERN FRONT END ENGINEER | FEB 2014 - MAY 2014

Learnt to built E-commerce sites on Magento Had a lot of exposure with clients to understand their requirements for the project